[Music]
I, Steven, take you,
Kendall, to be my wife.
And these things I promise you: I will
be faithful to you and honest with you.
I will respect and trust,
help and care for you.
From this day forward,
wherever you go, I go.
Whatever you face, I face.
In joy and in sorrow, in abundance
and in lack, in sickness and in health,
in every moment,
every season, I choose to love
and cherish you for as
long as we both shall live.
Come on, Steve! Let's go!
[Whispering] I'm proud of you.
I'm so happy. I love you.
I, Kendall, take you,
Steven, to be my husband.
And these things I promise you: I will
be faithful to you and honest with you.
I will respect and trust,
help and care for you.
From this day forward,
wherever you go, I go.
Whatever you face, I face.
In joy and in sorrow, and in abundance
and in lack, and in sickness and in health,
and in every moment and every
season, I choose to love
and cherish you for as
long as we both shall live.
Oh, wow.
Beautiful.
Kendall, I give you this ring as a sign
of my vow, and with all that I am
and all that I have, I honor
you in the name of the Father,
and of the Son, and of the Holy Spirit.
Steven, I give you this
ring as a sign of my vow,
and with all that I am
and all that I have,
I honor you in the name of the Father,
and of the Son, and of the Holy Spirit.
Steven, you may kiss your bride.
Please give it up, for the first time,
Kendall and Steven!
[Music]